[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 24, "question": "Did anyone see the speech where you are?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "anyone", "see", "the", "speech", "where", "you", "are", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 25, "answer": "No one will have seen it on state television and there's been no comment on state television about it.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "one", "will", "have", "seen", "it", "on", "state", "television", "and", "there", "'s", "been", "no", "comment", "on", "state", "television", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"]}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "PRP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "I mean the key thing, it seems to me, Nic, is we're still not really sure -- I don't think -- what this mission is, because there is a confusion between a position that says we don't want regime change, but we do want Gadhafi gone, isn't there?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "the", "key", "thing", ",", "it", "seems", "to", "me", ",", "Nic", ",", "is", "we", "'re", "still", "not", "really", "sure", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "--", "what", "this", "mission", "is", ",", "because", "there", "is", "a", "confusion", "between", "a", "position", "that", "says", "we", "do", "n't", "want", "regime", "change", ",", "but", "we", "do", "want", "Gadhafi", "gone", ",", "is", "n't", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "Well, the way it's read here is that this is the international coalition, the crusader army, as Gadhafi puts it, coming in on the side of the opposition to rebuild the sort of colonial footprint here, divide the country, steal the oil.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "way", "it", "'s", "read", "here", "is", "that", "this", "is", "the", "international", "coalition", ",", "the", "crusader", "army", ",", "as", "Gadhafi", "puts", "it", ",", "coming", "in", "on", "the", "side", "of", "the", "opposition", "to", "rebuild", "the", "sort", "of", "colonial", "footprint", "here", ",", "divide", "the", "country", ",", "steal", "the", "oil", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi", "Gadhafi"], "LOCATION": ["Sirte"]}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "What did you make of that development in this story?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "that", "development", "in", "this", "story", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "If that's the way this is going to take shape over the coming weeks and months, it's clearly going to be a very protracted affair, because the opposition really isn't in a place to face of against Gadhafi's army, even if you neutralize the army, their heavy weapons, their superiority, and advantage on the battlefield, what would seem today in Sirte, Gadhafi's hometown, is civilians with weapons.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "that", "'s", "the", "way", "this", "is", "going", "to", "take", "shape", "over", "the", "coming", "weeks", "and", "months", ",", "it", "'s", "clearly", "going", "to", "be", "a", "very", "protracted", "affair", ",", "because", "the", "opposition", "really", "is", "n't", "in", "a", "place", "to", "face", "of", "against", "Gadhafi", "'s", "army", ",", "even", "if", "you", "neutralize", "the", "army", ",", "their", "heavy", "weapons", ",", "their", "superiority", ",", "and", "advantage", "on", "the", "battlefield", ",", "what", "would", "seem", "today", "in", "Sirte", ",", "Gadhafi", "'s", "hometown", ",", "is", "civilians", "with", "weapons", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "Senator, what did you make of the speech?", "question_tokens": ["Senator", ",", "what", "did", "you", "make", "of", "the", "speech", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "Parts of it are very good.", "answer_tokens": ["Parts", "of", "it", "are", "very", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "I mean is that the kind of rebel army that we should be supporting?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "is", "that", "the", "kind", "of", "rebel", "army", "that", "we", "should", "be", "supporting", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "Here's what I do know.", "answer_tokens": ["Here", "'s", "what", "I", "do", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran"]}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "But isn't that exactly what people were saying in Iran before they were indeed taken over by extremists?", "question_tokens": ["But", "is", "n't", "that", "exactly", "what", "people", "were", "saying", "in", "Iran", "before", "they", "were", "indeed", "taken", "over", "by", "extremists", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "RB", "WP", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "Well, here's what happened in Iran.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "here", "'s", "what", "happened", "in", "Iran", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "General Myers, from a military perspective, is it satisfactory and clear enough for the military leaders that you have the president saying we don't want regime change, but we do want Gadhafi gone?", "question_tokens": ["General", "Myers", ",", "from", "a", "military", "perspective", ",", "is", "it", "satisfactory", "and", "clear", "enough", "for", "the", "military", "leaders", "that", "you", "have", "the", "president", "saying", "we", "do", "n't", "want", "regime", "change", ",", "but", "we", "do", "want", "Gadhafi", "gone", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNPS", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "Well, you know, I think so far so good.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "think", "so", "far", "so", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Myers", "Gadhafi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["next day"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["London"]}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "IN", ":", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "I mean are these the kind of people that we can trust to be the stable future government of this country that we presumably believe they can be?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "are", "these", "the", "kind", "of", "people", "that", "we", "can", "trust", "to", "be", "the", "stable", "future", "government", "of", "this", "country", "that", "we", "presumably", "believe", "they", "can", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "I think, Piers, we're going to learn a lot more as -- tomorrow, the next day, there's going to be a get-together in London, I think, to talk to some of the opposition leadership.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", ",", "Piers", ",", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "learn", "a", "lot", "more", "as", "--", "tomorrow", ",", "the", "next", "day", ",", "there", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "a", "get-together", "in", "London", ",", "I", "think", ",", "to", "talk", "to", "some", "of", "the", "opposition", "leadership", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "If we assume the president is right when we he says this is a humanitarian exercise, then what happens if these rebels begin to turn their guns on pro-Gadhafi supporters who are civilians?", "question_tokens": ["If", "we", "assume", "the", "president", "is", "right", "when", "we", "he", "says", "this", "is", "a", "humanitarian", "exercise", ",", "then", "what", "happens", "if", "these", "rebels", "begin", "to", "turn", "their", "guns", "on", "pro-Gadhafi", "supporters", "who", "are", "civilians", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "WP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "Well, that's the -- you know, that's always the question.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "the", "--", "you", "know", ",", "that", "'s", "always", "the", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "What do you think of the speech tonight?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "the", "speech", "tonight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "I think it's a great speech.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "great", "speech", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"]}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Where does that leave everybody?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "does", "that", "leave", "everybody", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "Well, I don't think so there is any chance for Gadhafi to stay in power.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "there", "is", "any", "chance", "for", "Gadhafi", "to", "stay", "in", "power", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "Middle East"]}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", ":", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "But right now, we're in a position where if Gadhafi hangs on, and America has not gone in with its full might, where does that leave everybody?", "question_tokens": ["But", "right", "now", ",", "we", "'re", "in", "a", "position", "where", "if", "Gadhafi", "hangs", "on", ",", "and", "America", "has", "not", "gone", "in", "with", "its", "full", "might", ",", "where", "does", "that", "leave", "everybody", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", ",", "CC", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "MD", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "It leaves -- it leaves America, it leaves the Middle East, it leaves the world in a very -- in a very terrible situation.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "leaves", "--", "it", "leaves", "America", ",", "it", "leaves", "the", "Middle", "East", ",", "it", "leaves", "the", "world", "in", "a", "very", "--", "in", "a", "very", "terrible", "situation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "POS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "How can you leave him there?", "question_tokens": ["How", "can", "you", "leave", "him", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "Let me play devil's advocate.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "play", "devil", "'s", "advocate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "Would you be happy as American president to have seen in the way that we did very unusually the French taking the lead followed by the British, and the Americans, you know, sending most of the forces in terms of all these, you know, missiles being fired, but not wanting to have the credit for doing that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "be", "happy", "as", "American", "president", "to", "have", "seen", "in", "the", "way", "that", "we", "did", "very", "unusually", "the", "French", "taking", "the", "lead", "followed", "by", "the", "British", ",", "and", "the", "Americans", ",", "you", "know", ",", "sending", "most", "of", "the", "forces", "in", "terms", "of", "all", "these", ",", "you", "know", ",", "missiles", "being", "fired", ",", "but", "not", "wanting", "to", "have", "the", "credit", "for", "doing", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "RBS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "VBG", "VBN", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "I don't quite understand that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "quite", "understand", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Syria"]}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "If they're so darned upset about us being in the Middle East, why would they ask him to intervene?", "question_tokens": ["If", "they", "'re", "so", "darned", "upset", "about", "us", "being", "in", "the", "Middle", "East", ",", "why", "would", "they", "ask", "him", "to", "intervene", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "What happens if -- as we're seeing now in Syria, for example, you're seeing the leadership there killing large numbers of people, ever increasing numbers of people.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "happens", "if", "--", "as", "we", "'re", "seeing", "now", "in", "Syria", ",", "for", "example", ",", "you", "'re", "seeing", "the", "leadership", "there", "killing", "large", "numbers", "of", "people", ",", "ever", "increasing", "numbers", "of", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Middle East"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "P.J. Crowley, did he sell it to you?", "question_tokens": ["P.J.", "Crowley", ",", "did", "he", "sell", "it", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "Yes, he did.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "he", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["P.J. Crowley"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Kosovo"]}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "Do you think that the way this coalition has now been constructed is likely to be an effective one?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "the", "way", "this", "coalition", "has", "now", "been", "constructed", "is", "likely", "to", "be", "an", "effective", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "I mean Kosovo is a very good example of where we did a bombing for 79 days.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "Kosovo", "is", "a", "very", "good", "example", "of", "where", "we", "did", "a", "bombing", "for", "79", "days", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Egypt", "Egypt"]}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "WRB", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "Are you absolutely confident that what everyone assumes was going to happen in Benghazi is what was going to happen?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "absolutely", "confident", "that", "what", "everyone", "assumes", "was", "going", "to", "happen", "in", "Benghazi", "is", "what", "was", "going", "to", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "Well, if you look at Egypt, the fundamental decision -- why Egypt worked the way it was is because the Egyptian military, from the outset, said very clearly, we are not going to turn our weapons on our own people.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "you", "look", "at", "Egypt", ",", "the", "fundamental", "decision", "--", "why", "Egypt", "worked", "the", "way", "it", "was", "is", "because", "the", "Egyptian", "military", ",", "from", "the", "outset", ",", "said", "very", "clearly", ",", "we", "are", "not", "going", "to", "turn", "our", "weapons", "on", "our", "own", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Benghazi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "Presumably, given that's what's happening in Syria and Yemen, you would want to go in there as well, would you?", "question_tokens": ["Presumably", ",", "given", "that", "'s", "what", "'s", "happening", "in", "Syria", "and", "Yemen", ",", "you", "would", "want", "to", "go", "in", "there", "as", "well", ",", "would", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "VBN", "IN", "POS", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "EX", "IN", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "Understand the predicates to military action.", "answer_tokens": ["Understand", "the", "predicates", "to", "military", "action", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Syria", "Yemen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clinton", "Gates"], "LOCATION": ["Middle East", "United States"]}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "At what point does America stop meddling in Middle Eastern affairs and look after it's own backyard?", "question_tokens": ["At", "what", "point", "does", "America", "stop", "meddling", "in", "Middle", "Eastern", "affairs", "and", "look", "after", "it", "'s", "own", "backyard", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "In fact, as Secretary Clinton and Secretary Gates said yesterday, the Middle East is, in fact, of vital interest to the United States.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "fact", ",", "as", "Secretary", "Clinton", "and", "Secretary", "Gates", "said", "yesterday", ",", "the", "Middle", "East", "is", ",", "in", "fact", ",", "of", "vital", "interest", "to", "the", "United", "States", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Middle Eastern"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Do you stand by those comments?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "stand", "by", "those", "comments", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "So do you feel that you were treated unfairly?", "question_tokens": ["So", "do", "you", "feel", "that", "you", "were", "treated", "unfairly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "I felt that under the circumstances, given the way that the issue emerged, it was my best step to resign.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "felt", "that", "under", "the", "circumstances", ",", "given", "the", "way", "that", "the", "issue", "emerged", ",", "it", "was", "my", "best", "step", "to", "resign", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "What was your reaction to President Obama's speech tonight?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "reaction", "to", "President", "Obama", "'s", "speech", "tonight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "Well, I think he's trying hard.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "trying", "hard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "When you hear President Obama say that he wants to get rid of Gadhafi, but he doesn't want regime change, does that make sense to you?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "hear", "President", "Obama", "say", "that", "he", "wants", "to", "get", "rid", "of", "Gadhafi", ",", "but", "he", "does", "n't", "want", "regime", "change", ",", "does", "that", "make", "sense", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "It makes no sense whatsoever.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "makes", "no", "sense", "whatsoever", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama", "Gadhafi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 383, "question": "And why aren't they paying for this?", "question_tokens": ["And", "why", "are", "n't", "they", "paying", "for", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "That's a very good point.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "very", "good", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "As a matter of principle, is it sensible that America gets involved in what is clearly a civil war in Libya?", "question_tokens": ["As", "a", "matter", "of", "principle", ",", "is", "it", "sensible", "that", "America", "gets", "involved", "in", "what", "is", "clearly", "a", "civil", "war", "in", "Libya", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "Well, I felt that the president was very presidential tonight.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "felt", "that", "the", "president", "was", "very", "presidential", "tonight", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "Libya"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "CC", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "Anthony Weiner, do you agree with that assessment?", "question_tokens": ["Anthony", "Weiner", ",", "do", "you", "agree", "with", "that", "assessment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "Yes, look, I think the sign that the president's probably on the right path is his critics are criticizing him in the same interview for going too far and not going far enough and fast enough.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "look", ",", "I", "think", "the", "sign", "that", "the", "president", "'s", "probably", "on", "the", "right", "path", "is", "his", "critics", "are", "criticizing", "him", "in", "the", "same", "interview", "for", "going", "too", "far", "and", "not", "going", "far", "enough", "and", "fast", "enough", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anthony Weiner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "If the Saudis and others are keen for America to step in and get rid of Gadhafi, why aren't they helping to pay for it?", "question_tokens": ["If", "the", "Saudis", "and", "others", "are", "keen", "for", "America", "to", "step", "in", "and", "get", "rid", "of", "Gadhafi", ",", "why", "are", "n't", "they", "helping", "to", "pay", "for", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CC", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "That's exactly the point the president made about not being willing to get stuck in.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "exactly", "the", "point", "the", "president", "made", "about", "not", "being", "willing", "to", "get", "stuck", "in", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "Gadhafi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1999"], "LOCATION": ["Kosovo"]}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "When you drop bombs on people, you're at war, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "drop", "bombs", "on", "people", ",", "you", "'re", "at", "war", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "I guess you don't remember the Kosovo engagement of 1999.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "guess", "you", "do", "n't", "remember", "the", "Kosovo", "engagement", "of", "1999", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Libya"]}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "IN", ",", "WRB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "VBG", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "What is your take on the strength of America here?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "take", "on", "the", "strength", "of", "America", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "It's interesting when we're talking about stepping in, when in fact you have other countries that are making Libya look like nice guys.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "interesting", "when", "we", "'re", "talking", "about", "stepping", "in", ",", "when", "in", "fact", "you", "have", "other", "countries", "that", "are", "making", "Libya", "look", "like", "nice", "guys", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Richardson"]}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "Are we winning for people that are friendly with Iran or al Qaeda?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "we", "winning", "for", "people", "that", "are", "friendly", "with", "Iran", "or", "al", "Qaeda", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "Governor Richardson, let me come back to you.", "answer_tokens": ["Governor", "Richardson", ",", "let", "me", "come", "back", "to", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "Why were you doing that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "were", "you", "doing", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "Well, I was shaking my head at you as well.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "shaking", "my", "head", "at", "you", "as", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "Governor Richardson, the intriguing thing about Gadhafi is that, of course, until recently, we were back on friendly terms with this murderous dictator, weren't we?", "question_tokens": ["Governor", "Richardson", ",", "the", "intriguing", "thing", "about", "Gadhafi", "is", "that", ",", "of", "course", ",", "until", "recently", ",", "we", "were", "back", "on", "friendly", "terms", "with", "this", "murderous", "dictator", ",", "were", "n't", "we", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Richardson", "Gadhafi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NATO"]}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "As a businessman, what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["As", "a", "businessman", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "Well, I think that's right, but I also say that NATO is us.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "'s", "right", ",", "but", "I", "also", "say", "that", "NATO", "is", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anthony Weiner"]}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "Why aren't they paying us for it?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "n't", "they", "paying", "us", "for", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "Anthony Weiner, you're still shaking your head.", "answer_tokens": ["Anthony", "Weiner", ",", "you", "'re", "still", "shaking", "your", "head", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "If the Arab League now say we need you in Syria, do we go?", "question_tokens": ["If", "the", "Arab", "League", "now", "say", "we", "need", "you", "in", "Syria", ",", "do", "we", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Arab League"], "LOCATION": ["Syria"]}}]